redleafads.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy policy

RedLeafAds.com has established its privacy policy to explain how your information within the purview of RedLeafAds.com is protected, collected and used. This policy may be updated by RedLeafAds.com. RedLeafAds.com will post notices of its policy changes on the RedLeafAds.com site at: <http://www.redleafads.com/help-privacy.html>  

**PRIVACY PROTECTION**

RedLeafAds.com does not share your information with third parties for marketing purposes, or engage in cross-marketing or link-referral programs with other similar sites. RedLeafAds.com recommends its customers to keep their password safe and do not remember it on public (shared) computers (Internet-cafe, college, library, family computer etc). RedLeafAds.com does not knowingly collect any information from persons under the age of 13. If RedLeafAds.com learns that a posting is by a person under the age of 13, RedLeafAds.com will remove that posting. RedLeafAds.com, or persons who post on RedLeafAds.com, may provide links to third party websites, with different privacy policies. RedLeafAds.com is not responsible for, nor have any control over, those third party websites.  

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

RedLeafAds.com collect traditional contact information such as your name, mailing and/or billing address, phone number and email address for few purposes: to send selfpublishing and confirmation emails, to authenticate user accounts, to provide subscription email services, to register for forums, to process any credit card charges, etc.

RedLeafAds.com does not store full credit card information but RedLeafAds.com may store the information partially, such as only last 4 digits of your credit card number for transactions authenticating, monitoring and fraud prevention purpose. All credit card transactions initiated by RedLeafAds.com are transmitted through a financial gateway using encrypted Secure Socket Layer (SSL 128 Bit) protocol.

Your personal information may be collected by RedLeafAds.com if you provide it in the feedback or comments, post it on our classifieds, forums, guestbook or other publishing areas of the website.

Should you expect your personal information to be private please do not post any personal information on RedLeafAds.com site. Standard web log entries for each page served, including visitor’s IP address, page URL, and timestamp are collected by RedLeafAds.com web logs in order to help diagnose problem with RedLeafAds.com servers, to administer RedLeafAds.com site, and to otherwise enhance visitor’s use of RedLeafAds.com sites and services. 

**DATA STORAGE**

RedLeafAds.com stores in its database all user generated content (classified ads, forums, guestbook postings etc.) even after they are deleted, as well as can archive such data elsewhere. RedLeafAds.com indefinitely stores web logs and other records. Registered members can access and update personal account information through the account homepage.  

**DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

RedLeafAds.com may disclose information about its users if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. RedLeafAds.com may also disclose information about its users to law enforcement officers or others, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms of Use; respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third-party; or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of RedLeafAds.com, its users or the general public. RedLeafAds.com complies with the provisions of C.R.S. § 6-1-716 pertinent to the breaches of security notifications effective September 1st, 2006.  

**GLOBAL USE**

By providing us with data and by visiting RedLeafAds.com you acknowledge and agree that due to the global use of RedLeafAds.com we may use the data collected in the course of your use of our site and/or services for the purposes identified in this policy or in our other communications to you, including the transmission of information outside your resident jurisdiction. Data provided to RedLeafAds.com may be stored on servers throughout different jurisdictions. User agrees to consent to transfer of such data to different locations.  

**IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH RedLeafAds.com PRIVACY POLICY PLEASE LEAVE THIS WEBSITE**
